(SOFT MUSIC)
♪ AT FIRST I WAS AFRAID,
I WAS PETRIFIED ♪
♪ KEPT THINKING I COULD NEVER
LIVE WITHOUT YOU BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ BUT THEN I SPENT
SO MANY NIGHTS ♪
♪ THINKING HOW
YOU DID ME WRONG ♪
♪ AND I GREW STRONG ♪
♪ AND I LEARNED
HOW TO GET ALONG ♪
♪ AND SO YOU'RE BACK ♪
♪ FROM OUTER SPACE ♪
♪ I JUST WALKED IN
TO FIND YOU HERE ♪
♪ WITH THAT SAD LOOK
UPON YOUR FACE ♪
♪ I SHOULD HAVE CHANGED
THAT STUPID LOCK ♪
♪ I SHOULD HAVE MADE
YOU LEAVE YOUR KEY ♪
♪ IF I'D KNOWN FOR JUST
ONE SECOND YOU'D BE BACK ♪
♪ TO BOTHER ME ♪
♪ GO ON NOW, GO,
WALK OUT THE DOOR ♪
♪ JUST TURN AROUND NOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
WELCOME ANYMORE ♪
♪ WEREN'T YOU THE ONE WHO
TRIED TO HURT ME WITH GOODBYE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D CRUMBLE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D
LAY DOWN AND DIE ♪
♪ OH NO, NOT I, I WILL SURVIVE ♪
♪ OH, AS LONG AS I KNOW HOW TO
LOVE, I KNOW I'LL STAY ALIVE ♪
♪ I'VE GOT ALL MY LIFE TO LIVE ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT ALL MY LOVE
TO GIVE AND I'LL SURVIVE ♪
♪ I WILL SURVIVE, HEY, HEY ♪
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ IT TOOK ALL THE STRENGTH
I HAD NOT TO FALL APART ♪
♪ KEPT TRYING HARD TO MEND THE
PIECES OF MY BROKEN HEART ♪
♪ AND I SPENT
OH-SO MANY NIGHTS ♪
♪ JUST FEELING
SORRY FOR MYSELF ♪
♪ I USED TO CRY ♪
♪ BUT NOW I HOLD MY HEAD
UP HIGH AND YOU SEE ME ♪
♪ SOMEBODY NEW ♪
♪ I'M NOT THAT CHAINED-UP
LITTLE PERSON ♪
♪ STILL IN LOVE WITH YOU ♪
♪ AND SO YOU FELT
LIKE DROPPING IN ♪
♪ AND JUST EXPECT
ME TO BE FREE ♪
♪ WELL, NOW I'M
SAVING ALL MY LOVIN' ♪
♪ FOR SOMEONE WHO'S LOVING ME ♪
♪ GO ON NOW, GO,
WALK OUT THE DOOR ♪
♪ JUST TURN AROUND NOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
WELCOME ANYMORE ♪
♪ WEREN'T YOU THE ONE WHO TRIED
TO BREAK ME WITH GOODBYE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D CRUMBLE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D
LAY DOWN AND DIE ♪
♪ OH NO, NOT I, I WILL SURVIVE ♪
♪ OH, AS LONG AS I KNOW HOW TO
LOVE, I KNOW I'LL STAY ALIVE ♪
♪ I'VE GOT ALL MY LIFE TO LIVE ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT ALL MY LOVE
TO GIVE AND I'LL SURVIVE ♪
♪ I WILL SURVIVE ♪
♪ OH ♪
♪ GO ON NOW, GO,
WALK OUT THE DOOR ♪
♪ JUST TURN AROUND NOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
WELCOME ANYMORE ♪
♪ WEREN'T YOU THE ONE WHO TRIED
TO BREAK ME WITH GOODBYE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D CRUMBLE ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'D
LAY DOWN AND DIE ♪
♪ OH NO, NOT I, I WILL SURVIVE ♪
♪ OH, AS LONG AS I KNOW HOW TO
LOVE, I KNOW I'LL STAY ALIVE ♪
♪ I'VE GOT ALL MY LIFE TO LIVE ♪
♪ AND I'VE GOT ALL MY LOVE
TO GIVE AND I'LL SURVIVE ♪
♪ I WILL SURVIVE ♪